Contact

c0blak01@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/courtney-blakely-b4aa751a2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Public Speaking
Faith-based

Courtney Blakely

Travel Nurse & Public Speaker

Washington D.C. Metro Area

Summary

Travel Nurse experienced in providing and coordinating patient care. Patient care advocate and educator. Emotional support for both patients and families.

Specializing in Neuroscience nursing care management of the following; ischemic and hemorrhagic strokes, seizure disorders, hydrocephalus, EVD management, neurosurgeries, neurovascular surgeries, and intensive care.

Also, skilled in faith-based writing and public speaking.

Experience

Emerald Health Services
Travel Nurse
March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Norton Healthcare Registered Nurse August 2017 - February 2019 (1 year 7 months)

Education

Spalding University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2015 - 2017)

University of Louisville Nursing